Mihai Eniu

WEB AND BACKEND (NODE.JS, PYTHON, PHP) DEVELOPER



- Cluj-Napoca, Cluj, Romania
- mihai@htg-software.com
- Portfolio cv.htg-software.com
- **4** +40 743 018 109
- in in/MihaiEniu

ABSTRACT

Freelance Backend and Fullstack developer with experience in JavaScript (React.js; React Native; Next.js; Node.js;) PHP, Python, C++, HTML and CSS, looking for an opportunity to prove my worth.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Node.js (Express)

Python (Django)

••••••

PHP (Symphony, Laravel)

React.js (Tailwind CSS)

•••••

• • • • • • •

• • • • • •

Docker

NoSQL (PostgreSQL)

Bootstrap

• • • • • •

WORK EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE WEB/BACKEND DEVELOPER

HTG-software EU SRL, RO

May 2020 - Present

- Coming up with unique Website and Backend designs and structures for clients using technologies such as JavaScript, Python and PHP (with frameworks).
- · Worked with SQL and NoSQL databases
- Gained experience working with and configuring Linuxbased servers (CentOS) for hosting and application environments

CO-AUTHOR OF CONFERENCE PAPER PUBLICATION

SMC Malaga, Spain

May 2019

 "Composing with Sounds: Designing an Object-Oriented <u>DAW for the Teaching of Sound-Based Composition"</u>
presents and discusses the specific approach used when designing the application "Compose with Sounds" and its implications in Object-based Music Composition.

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

University of Portsmouth, UK Oct 2018 - Jan 2020

- Required participation in various research projects internal or external to the University as a sub-contracted developer.
- During the collaboration with DeMontford University in Leicester for the development of "Compose With Sounds". Responsabilities included converting the MacOS-only application to run on Windows and Linux and collaboratively develop and design the mobile version of the application (Known as Compose with Sounds Live). Both of which have been developed in C++.

TEACHING DEMONSTRATOR

University of Portsmouth, UK Sep 2017 - Jan 2020

- The position initially involved assisting other lecturers in practical tutorials and workshops with large groups of students, but eventually developed in covering four units as a sole lecturer for a semester (Sabatical Cover).
- Two of the units covered throughout were "Audio Programming" and "Sound and Music Programming" and both featured designing Applications and Audio Plugins using C++ and the Juce Framework. Another unit was "Digital Sound" which thought students how to use Max MSP

EDUCATION HISTORY

BSC IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND NETWORKING

Open University, UK

Oct 2019 - Present

- Distance learning degree with focus on application development and network engineering.
- Development using Next.js as a all-in-one web solution
- Robotics design using Python and Raspberry Pi singleboard computers and GPIO connectivity
- Network design using hardware and virtual devices as to maximise security and coverage in both LAN and VLAN

PHD, APPLICATIONS OF MACHINE LEARNING IN MUSIC PEDAGOGY

University of Portsmouth, UK Oct 2018 - Present

- The research question tries to uncover whether implementing Machine Learning Models into a pedagogical environment for a lecturer-centric subject, e.g Music Theory, could positively influence the adoption rate of the teaching materials.
- A teaching and testing environment has been developed using Python using camera recognition components in combination with algorithmic timing to analyse learning patterns and restructure the teaching and testing materials as to maximise learning.

MSC IN MUSIC TECHNOLOGY

University of Portsmouth, UK Sep 2017 - Sep 2180

- The research question for the Master asked whether integrating a small form-factor computer into a Eurorack Modular Synthesiser could be a viable product in an oversaturated market.
- A Eurorack module has also been constructed and presented as part of the Final Submission which featured a LattePanda computer running an application developed using Juce and C++ for multi-track recording and Audio Effects stacking.

BSC IN MUSIC AND SOUND TECHNOLOGY

University of Portsmouth, UK Sep 2014 - Jul 2017

- · Graduated with First Class Honours
- Degree focused on the various uses of technology in Music and Sound creation, processing, recording and composition. As part of the School of Creative Technologies, there were units shared among other courses thus promoting cross-subject collaborations between students.
- The Final Year Dissertation project showcased the process of creating an audio middleware software using Unity and Max MSP.

ABOUT

Having lived, studied, thought and worked in the United Kingdom for 6 years opened my eyes to new technologies and means of communicating with people, while giving me the opportunity to hone in my knowledge in various coding languages and practices.

Throughout my journey from a first year student to a freelance worker, I have developed myself with every chance I had

LANGUAGE SKILLS

C1 - Profecient

A2 - Beginner

C2 - Native



A2 - Beginner

SOFT SKILLS

Teamwork

• • • • • •

Leadership

Adaptability

Problem Solving

Analytic Thinking

• • • • • • •

.....

Agile Methodology

References available on request